http://www.gardenofpraise.com/privacy.htm

Login or register for tests, newsletters and community.
PRIVACY POLICY
Patsy Stevens at Garden of Praise has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate her firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Garden of Praise.
Garden of Praise is not a company. It is not even a registered non-profit organization. It is an individual effort by the webmaster to create the content you see and hear. All inquiries about Garden of Praise should be directed to Patsy Stevens. This privacy statement was created so that you will have better information about how your personal information is stored and used at this site.
Use of Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). We have no access to or control over these advertising cookies.
You may choose to turn off cookies in your browser. This site
will still work for the most part.
Advertisers
We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense, etc. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.
* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Use of Log Files
Like most web sites, this site uses log files. These log files store internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Opt-in Newsletter
This site's registration feature is limited to opt-in newsletter subscription. The only information you are required to provide to receive the newsletter is your email address. You can unsubscribe at any time to this newsletter using the form at the bottom of many pages.
Use of Your Personal Data
Personal information you provide to this site will NEVER be distributed to third parties without your prior consent.
External Links
This site contains links to hundreds of other sites. Care has been made to link only to clean, useful sites, but content is constantly changing and this site cannot be held responsible for the privacy practices or content of these linked sites. Please protect your family from the dangers of the internet. Never leave a child unattended with free access to the internet. It is very easy to find dangerous content.
Credit Card Processing
This site uses Paypal for credit card processing. All credit card numbers are stored in Paypal and cannot be accessed by the site owner. Please, never send your credit card number in an unsecure email. It is not safe and I cannot process your payment this way.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with Garden of Praise, please contact:
Patsy Stevens
Contact Mrs. Stevens by email.
